Alright, we've cut our paper and put down our sticky strip.
The next thing were going to do is assemble them.
I've already peeled off the red top layer on the sticky strip on this one, and all you're going to do is roll it like a toilet paper roll, because that's what it's going to resemble when you get it done.
So roll that, and then you can see this sticky strip, you're going to go ahead and press that side down, and then you're going to press this side the opposite way.
But, before we seal this up, we need to put something really fun in it.
This is a good time where the kids could buy their mom some chocolates, where they could put a little note into their mom, or maybe a bracelet or some diamonds, anything like that is nice.
So, were going to go ahead and put some chocolates, I've just got some Hershey's nuggets in here.
So we've pushed one, one way, were going to push one the other way, and then were going to take our crimper, and this is just going to kind of help seal the edges.
Alright, so we?re going to run it through, place it in the handle, and then were going to go about, one, two, three, back and forth a couple times just to keep that edge nice and tight.
The same way on this side, and it looks just like those sour cream containers that you used to be able to get.
I'm not sure if there still out there, but they used to be out there at any of the restaurants and stuff that had things to go.
So, real quickly I'm going to do it again.
Just roll it up, so it resembles like a tube of your empty toilet paper roll.
Crimp those edges, seal them together, throw in some more chocolates.
If a little chocolate is good, more is better.
Seal that edge, slide it in your crimper, back and forth, two or three times, to help seal that edge, and there we have two sour cream containers already prefilled with chocolate.
The next thing I'm going to do is show what other things you can do with these really cute sour cream containers.